Guide to the John W. Hollister papers,ca. 1980-1990.
Hollister, John W. papers,ca. 1980-1990
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John W. Hollister papers, ca. 1980-1990.
7685
John W. Hollister
2 c.f. and 1 o-s folder.
Printed materials, manuscripts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Notes, announcements, brochures, and publications from gay rights and AIDS organizations in Binghamton, Ithaca, and nationally.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Notes, announcements, brochures, and publications from gay rights and AIDS organizations in Binghamton, Ithaca, and nationally.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hollister, John W.
Subjects:
AIDS (Disease)--Political aspects--United States.; Gay liberation movement.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- ACT UP/ Gay Pride NYC, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AIDS (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AIDS- Lesbian (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AIDS- Public Opinion (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AIDS Study and Gay Health (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Amherst (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Atlanta/South (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Black, People of Color (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Canada (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cape Cod Provincetown on Cape Cod (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Colorado (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Czech (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Defense Against Violence (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Direct Mail- Political Fundraising (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Elmira (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ESPA (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Examples of Research Questionnaires (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Feminist Men (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Florida (Box 1, Folder 19)
- GAGV Poster (Box 1, Folder 20)
- GALA (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Gay and Left Democratic Left. May/June 1991. New York, New York. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Gay Money (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Gay Alcoholics (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Gay Commodities (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Gay Community News (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Gay Film Info., Recordings, etc. (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Gay Film Chicago, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Gay Parents (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Gay Priest (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Gay Religion (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Gay Rights National Lobby (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Gay Youth, IPLGY (Box 1, Folder 33)
- GLAD (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Grants- Resist (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Herizon (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Lambda Legal (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Latino (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Lavender Hill Mob (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Legislation (Box 1, Folder 40)
- L/G Network- Mobilization for Survival (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Local Reactionaries (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Los Angeles (Box 1, Folder 43)
- March on Washington- Papers/Leaflets (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Midwest (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 46)
- "The Art of AIDS Awareness" exhibit catalog, Princeton, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Boise, ID Stonewall 25 minutes & other misc. gay ephemeraMiscellaneous Democracy's Poet: Walt Whitman, A Celebration. Stonewall 25 National Steering Committee Meeting, October 22nd. Boise, ID. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous International (Box 2, Folder 3)
- National Visibility Campaign '88, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- NGTF (Box 2, Folder 5)
- NGLTF (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NYC Gay Pride March '88, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- NY Gay Pride '89, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NY State Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 9)
- NYSLGL (Box 2, Folder 10)
- OregonNYSLGL (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Pamphlets Worth Reproducing (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Pride at Work- Out and Organizing T-shirt (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Puerto Rico- Calender (Box 2, Folder 15)
- People with AIDS (PWA) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Religion Christianity and Crisis: A Christian Journal of Opinion. Sept. 21, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Rochester (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Romonovski & Phillips (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Safe Sex/AIDS Info (Box 2, Folder 20)
- San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Seattle (Box 2, Folder 22)
- S/M (Box 2, Folder 23)
- STAP (Southern Tier AIDS Program) (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Stonewall 25 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Syracuse Syracuse Cultural Workers: Catalog of Posters, Cards, Peace Calendar. Spring/Summer 1987, Syracuse, NY. (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Thornfield Workshop on Sexuality (Box 2, Folder 27)
- US- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Utica (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Washington, DC (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Male prostitution article, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Socialist newspapers, gay stories, 1984-1988 The Freedom Socialist. Seattle, WA. Socialist Worker. Chicago, IL. Torch: Newspaper of the Revolutionary Socialist League. New York, NY. Workers World. New York, NY. (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Regional newspapers, gay stories, 1981-1996 The Boston Review. Vol 11, no. 6. Boston, MA. The Hoboken Reporter. Vol. 7, No. 25. Hoboken, NJ. One in Ten: The Publication. March 1996. Boston, MA. The Valley Advocate. March 28-April 3, 1996. Hatfield, MA. (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Articles, gays on campus 1985, 86, 91 Gay Harvard Alumni/ae Newsletter. Vol. 3 No. 3. Cambridge, MA. The Graduate Quill. March, 1991. Buffalo, NY. OFF: Serving the off campus community. Dec. 3, 1986., 1985, 1986, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Misc. articles: 1990 NY Pride, 1985 military recruiting Temple University Temple University News. Feb. 5, 1985. Philadelphia, PA. What A Gay Day! (Excerpt from the New York Post). June 25, 1990. New York, NY., 1990, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Syracuse night life article, 1996 Syracuse New Times: The Central New York Alternative. Jan 31-Feb 7, 1996. Syracuse, NY. (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Sin Fronteras Article (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Special issues of magazines on gays & AIDS, 1985-1993 The Atlantic. Vol. 271 no. 3. Boston, MA. (Box 2, Folder 38)
- SYOL Newsletter Floppy Disk, no date (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Save Your Own Lives Original Stickers and Pins (Envelope from John Hollister), no date (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Misc. Gay Fliers and Announcements, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 3)
- The Other Voice, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Broome County Gay Alliance Bulletin, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Other (Gay) Periodicals, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- The Other Voice, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- The Other Voice, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Gay Space Magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- The Other Voice, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Amethyst, Vol. 2, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Amethyst Advertising Materials, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Amethyst Miscellaneous Materials, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Amethyst Submission Materials, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Space Materials, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Space Administrative Materials, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Space-Affiliated Events, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Space Correspondence, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 18)
- SYOL Bylaws, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 19)
- SYOL Photographs, June/July 1990s (Box 3, Folder 20)
- SYOL Safety Programs, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 21)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Amethyst, Vol. 3-4, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Space Finances, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- SYOL Board Meeting Agendas and Materials, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Tax Status of SYOL Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Tax Status of SYOL Forms, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Tax Status of SYOL Incorporation Documents, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Tax Status of SYOL Instructions, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Space Meeting Agenda, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances Tabulations, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Amethyst, Vol. 5, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- SYOL Board Meeting Agendas and Materials, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Amethyst, Vol. 6, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Amethyst, Vol. 7, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Amethyst, Vol. 8, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Amethyst, Vol. 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Amethyst, Vol. 10, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- SYOL Budgets and Finances, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Amethyst, Vol. 11, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- SYOL Board Agendas and Materials, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Amethyst, Vol. 12, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Amethyst, Vol. 13, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Amethyst, Vol. 14, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Milestone Magazine, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Binghamton Area Rainbow Association (BARA), Successor to SYOL, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- The Truth- AIDS is Germ Warfare! New York, NY. (Map-case Folder 1)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Formation Materials, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Volunteer Materials, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Call Logs, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Call Logs, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Call Logs, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Call Logs, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Line - Call Logs (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Resource Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Gay Ads and Organizations, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Other Gay Resource Lines, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Other General Resource Lines, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Gay Peer Counseling - Cornell, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Other Peer Counseling Materials, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Pride Agenda Materials, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Binghamton area gay, lesbian, bisexual events, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Harpur Gay Alliance, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Gay People's Union (formerly Harpur Gay Alliance), 1980s (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Gay People's Union sponsored events, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Diversity Works - Heterosexism Awareness, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 20)
- ZAP - Heterosexism Education, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Awareness Week - SUNY Stony Brook, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- "Our Press" Boycott - Binghamton, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Binghamton - AIDS Programs and Events, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Student Association of the State University of New York (esp. LGB Caucus), 1990s (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Binghamton M*A*S*H*S*U*N*Y Event, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Binghamton - Historical Gay Articles, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Binghamton Area Homophobic Literature, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 28)
- MOO! SUNY Humor Magazine Homophobia, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Gay People's Union Sit-In on Binghamton campus, November 1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Gay People's Union sponsored events, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Gay People's Union counter to Pipe Dream (SUNY-Binghamton student newspaper), 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 31)
- The Rising Tide and Looking Left Papers, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Gynegraph and other papers, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Hera - Binghamton Women's Center Paper, 1984-1996 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Community Gay Newsjournal - Albany, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- The Eagle's Cry Gay Paper - Elmira, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Gulf Gayzette - Greater Utica Paper, 1989, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Health Enhancement/Awareness Research, Training, and Services (HEALTH) materials - Binghamton, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- TARA Events, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- ACT-UP Materials, 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Local Binghamton Political Action, 1988-1996 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Binghamton Bears, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Binghamton AIDS Quilt Project, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- GLSG Materials, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Gay Businesses - Binghamton area, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Collected P-Flag Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Prejudice and Pride Event - Binghamton, April 1990 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- SUNY-Binghamton campus events, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 48)
- LGB Activism in Washington DC, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 49)
- National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF) Creating Change Conference, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- New York City Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Gay and Lesbian Graduate Organization at SUNY-Binghamton, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Lesbian and Gay Studies Coalition Graduate Student Organization at SUNY-Binghamton, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Contested Sexualities Conference II at SUNY-Binghamton, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Lesbian and Gay Film Festival (part of Contested Sexualities Conference II), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Contested Sexualities Conference III at SUNY-Binghamton, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- AIDS and LGBT Politics Stickers, Trojan Condom, no date (Box 5, Folder 1)
- International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission, no date (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Worksheet for Opponents of the Family Protection Act, no date (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Work-Study Group on Homosexuality: Report, no date (Box 5, Folder 4)
- David Goodstein, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bibliographies and Catalogues, 1975-1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- The Gay Left Collective, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Uses of the Erotic: The Erotic as Power: Speech, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Newsletters/ Press Clippings, 1978-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Gay and Lesbian Liberation in Mexico- Clippings and Paper by Hollister, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- LGBT Articles, 1979-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Poem- Charley Shively, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Pamphlets (1), 1980-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Lavender Left, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Radical Faerie Circle Collective and Dialogue with John Preston, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Democratic Socialists of America, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- John Preston- Article, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- New Alliance Party, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- LGBT Men and Women of Color, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Feminist Publications, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- GAYPAC, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Lesbian and Gay Political Action and Discussion Group, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Radical Press Clippings, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Pamphlets (2), 1984-1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Book Reviews, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Faerie Gatherings, 1985-1999 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Announcements and Press Releases, 1986-1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Publications, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Newspapers, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- LBGT Studies International Conference, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Samaritan College, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Porn Wars, 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Yale Conference, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- The Yale Incident, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- News Clippings, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Lesbian and Gay Studies Conference at Harvard, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Lesbian and Gay Studies Syllabi, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Sociologists' Lesbian and Gay Caucus, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Lesbian and Gay Studies Conference at Rutgers, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Petitions, Surveys, and Votes, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Philadelphia Gay News- Latinos and AIDS, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- NGLTF, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Calls for Submissions, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Event and Organization Advertising, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- LAGLS News- Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Scientists, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Society of Lesbian and Gay Anthropologists, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- LGBT Guides- Pennsylvania, 1993-2009 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Queer Theory Indeed- The Sixth North American Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Studies Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- LGBT Resources and Organizations Lists, 1994-2001 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Behind Our Backs- Magazine, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Lesbian and Gay History- Defining a Field, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Committee on Lesbian and Gay History, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- LGBT Guides, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Equality Forum Program Book- The Global GLBT Event, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- LGBT Guides to New Jersey and New York, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Humboldt Society- Philadelphia, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- French Program Guides, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Gays in Latin America (1), 1980-1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Gays in Cuba, 1980-1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Newsletters (1), 1981-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- "No Business as Usual", 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Newspapers (1), 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Fliers and Event Calendars, 1983-1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Gays in Latin America (2), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Ithaca Men's Network, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Gays in Nicaragua, 1984-1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Ithaca Lesbian and Gay Task Force (ILGTF), 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico- Collectivo de Concientizacion Gay, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Out of the Darkness, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Governor's Task Force on Bias-Related Violence, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Newsletters (2), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Newspapers (2), 1990-1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Pamphlets and Information, 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Index on Censorship, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ultra Violet, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Cataloged as a HSC collection except for items marked with an asterisk.
Above Ground: News in the Lehigh Valley. August 1996. Allentown, PA.
A Different Light Review: A Catalog of Gay and Lesbian Literature. Spring 1991. New York, NY.
Alabama Forum. Vol. 17 no 11. Birmingham, AL.
Aldyne, Nathan. Vermilion. New York: Ballantine Books, 1980.
Alternatives: The Personal Introduction Service for the Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Communities. Albany, NY.
American Book Review. Vol. 9 no. 4. Boulder, CO.
American Sociological Association Newsletter- Section on Sex and Gender- Spring 1993, Fall 1993, Spring 1994.
Art and Understanding- January/February 1993.
Au Courant: The Delaware Valley's Largest Gay/Lesbian Circulation. Philadelphia, PA. (5)
B&G: A Different Point of View. Vol. 1 no. 4. New York, NY.
Back-Talk- June-July 1993.
The Barrister- April 1986.
Bay Windows: New England's Largest Lesbian and Gay Newspaper. Boston, MA. (5)
Being Alive: People with AIDS Action Coalition. Los Angeles, CA. (2)
Blackleather- Spring/Summer 1997
Black/Out: The Magazine of the National Coalition of Black Lesbians and Gays. Vo. 1 no. 1. Washington, DC.
Blade: The Cutting Edge from Orange County & Long Beach. #3.5. Laguna Beach, CA.
Campbell, Michael. Lord Dismiss Us. Chicago: University of Chicago Press, 1967.Bay Windows: New England's Largest Lesbian and Gay Newspaper. Boston, MA. (5)
Capital Xtra: Ottawa's Lesbian & Gay Monthly. May 19, 1995. Ottawa, Canada.Bay Windows: New England's Largest Lesbian and Gay Newspaper. Boston, MA. (5)
The Center Voice: Lesbian & Gay Community Services Newsletter. Vol. 6 No. 3. New York, NY.
CLAGS- Newsletter for the Center on Lesbian and Gay Studies- Fall 1992, Spring 1993, Fall 1993, Spring 1994, Fall 1994, Summer 1996.
Cofrancesco, Joan. Walpurgis night. La Jolla, CA: San Diego Poets Press, 1993.
Come to Long Island! Vol. 4 No. 10. (Advertising Supplement)
Coming Up! The Lesbian/Gay Community Calendar of Events and Newspaper for the Bay Area. San Francisco, CA. (3)
Committee on Lesbian and Gay History- Newsletter- December 1987, September 1993, January 1994, January 1995, May 1995, September 1995, January/March 1997, May/September 1997.
Community Yellow Pages: Southern California's Gay and Lesbian Telephone Book. 1994.
Community: the Capital District's lesbian, gay and bi newsmonthly. Albany, NY. (Plus Inserts) (32)
Conference Report: New York State Gay/Lesbian Conference. Syracuse, NY. (5)
The Connection: The STAP Newsletter. Johnson City, NY. (48)
Crossroads: Supporting lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender youth. Vol. 2, nos. 3 & 4. Philadelphia, PA.
CUGALA- Cornell University Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association Newsletter- Spring 1993, Winter/Spring 1994, Spring 1996, Spring 1997.
CUSLAR Newsletter- February 1985 (Cornell University Committee on US- Latin America Relations).
The Danny: New York State's Premier Entertainment Guide. Vol. 1 no. 2., May 1990. Rochester, NY.
Destiny Star- 1998 Fall Edition, 1998 Post Mud Season Edition, 1998 Solstice Edition, May 1999 (Issues Number 5, 6, 7, 9).
Digest: The Newsletter of the World Congress of Gay & Lesbian Jewish Organizations. Spring 1984. San Francisco, CA.
Draghead: exploring faeriedom + fey arts. Spring/Summer 1992, Autumn 1992, Spring 1993, Spring 1994, Summer 1994, Winter 1995. Ontario, Canada.
Drummer- 1993, 1996, 1997
Edge Magazine. Los Angeles, CA. (2)
Elite. Vol. 1 No. 6. Oakdale, NY.
Empathy- Fall/Winter 1989/1990.
The Empty Closet. Rochester, NY. (1)
Eros- 1993
Faerie.Gram- January 1994, April 1994, Wort Moon 1994, Snow Moon 1995.
The Fifth Column. Syracuse, NY. (4)
The fight for lesbian rights benefits all women. New York, NY.
Fisher, Pete. Special Teachers/Special Boys. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1979.
Frontiers. West Hollywood, CA. (2)
Gai Pied Hebdo. No. 77.
Gay & Lesbian Times: Southern California's Weekly. #345. San Diego, CA.
The Gay Book. Third Edition, Autumn/Winter 1985-86. San Francisco, CA.
Gay Community News. Boston, MA. (2)
Gay Games IV Official Program. June 1994. San Francisco, CA.
GAYPAC- Gay People At Cornell News- October 1983, November 1983, December 1983, March 1984, April/May 1984.
Gay Scotland. May/June 1986. Edinburgh, Scotland.The Empty Closet. Rochester, NY. (1)
Gay Times: Incorporated Gay News. May 1993. London, England.
Gayzette: Serving the Gay, Lesbian, & Bisexual Community of Greater Utica. Utica, NY. (Plus Inserts) (65)
GLAAD Reports, LA. July 1994. Los Angeles, CA.
GLAD Briefs. Spring 1984. Boston, MA.
GLBTF Newsletter (Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Task Force)- Winter 1993, Spring 1993, Summer 1993
GLPCI Network. Montclair, NJ. (2)
The Guide: Gay Travel, Entertainment, Politics, and Sex. Boston, MA. (6)
The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review- Fall 1998.
Hera: A Forum for the Binghamton Women's Community. Binghamton, NY. (62)
HMI Report Card: Newsletter of the Hetrick-Martin Institute. Summer 1991.
Holleran, Andrew. Night in Aruba. New York: William Morrow and Company, Inc., 1983.
Homo Xtra. New York, NY. (12)
Hunt- 1990.
Icon Magazine. Sept. 1997. New York, NY.
IGLA Bulletin (International Gay and Lesbian Archives)- Spring/Summer 1994
Images- Summer 2001.
Information About AIDS for the Columbia Community. Colombia University Health Service: 1986.
In Touch- 1976.
In Unity and The Gay Christian. Los Angeles, CA. (7)
Ithaca Men's Network- May 1984, January 1985, February 1985, April 1985.
The James White Review- Spring 1987, Summer 1987, Fall 1987, Winter 1988, Spring/Summer 1988, Winter 1989, Fall 1989, Winter 1990, Winter 1991, Winter 1994.
Kopkind, Andrew. The Gay Moment (from The Nation). May 3, 1993. New York, NY.
LA Alternatives: National Lesbian and Gay Journalists Association. San Francisco, CA. (2)
Lambda Rising News. Autumn 1993. Washington, DC.
Lambda Update. New York, New York. (3)
LA Weekly. Vol. 16 no. 36. Los Angeles, CA.
The Lavender Letter: an LGCN Publication. Oneonta, NY. (8)
The Lesbian and Gay Left Collective- Article, no date (Title: Lesbian and Gay Rights: What's In It for You? A Pamphlet for Progressive People)
Lesbian and Gay Studies Newsletter- LGSN- November 1989, March 1990, July 1990, November 1990, March 1991, July 1991, November 1991, March 1992, July 1992, July 1993, March 1995.
Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Resource Center- Cornell University- Annual Newsletter, Winter 2000.
The Lesbian News. Los Angeles, CA. (2)